SHAH SOLEHRIA







+1 (604) 358-1493

Summary

Built my first .NET web app seven years ago at British Columbia Institute of Technology (BCIT)!

Professional proficient with full-stack SAAS applications written in Python, Java, or JavaScript; Expertise in "DevOps" & "Site Reliability Engineering" at enterprise scale! Excels at overseeing: change management, optimizing performance, & designing secure infrastructure.

EducationBC Institute of Technology

❖ Bachelor of Business AdministrationDegreeJun 2018-Dec 2020❖ Business IT ManagementDiplomaSept 2016-May 2018

Notable Academia

Udemy

Web Security & Bug Bounty

Dec 2023

Decoding DevOps with Projects

Aug 2023

AZ-303 Azure Architecture Technologies

Dec 2021

❖ AZ-104 Microsoft Azure Administrator

Aug 2021 Aug 2021

❖ AWS Certified Solutions Architect Associate

Work Experience

DevOps / Site Reliability Engineering Delta, BC

shahdevelopment

May 2023-Present

- Re-engineered static JavaScript (JS) website into API architecture with new: front end, back end, & with at rest code security in GitHub.
- Designed Docker images & engineered shahdevelopment site to run in a Docker Swarm Cluster.
- Integrated existing Docker images into functional Kubernetes Cluster running in AWS cloud: https://kubernetes.shahdevelopment.tech/
- Used Jenkins Plugins and tools to setup testing with Sonargube, Docker builds, & artifact storage.
- Developed complete CI/CD for shahdevelopment site with Jenkins build pipelines.

Migration Engineer (Project)

Rivermeadow

Feb 2023-May 2023

Remote

- Automated extraction, transformation, & loading of large datasets using Python Pandas & VBA scripts.
- Successfully executed migrations from VMWARE to Azure: utilizing JSON log servers, past tickets, & Slack for troubleshooting.
- Conducted thorough pre & post migration validation testing & implemented change management strategies.
- Designed batch scripts automating post-migration checks, system monitoring, & maintenance.

Sr. Network Admin (Closed)

Electrameccanica

Burnaby, BC

Dec 2022-Feb 2023

- Engineered Windows migrations: prepped landing zone (Azure) & adapted Hyper-V disks.
- Quickly learned to how to deal with Fortinet FortiGate firewalls: designed SDWAN on existing ADVPN Dynamic VPN tunneling.
- Assumed responsibility over Linux-based Zscaler application (resolved a site-wide outage).
- Helped sell laptops & uninstall IT equipment for shipping to Arizona.

System Administrator

CaseIQ

Remote Jan 2022–Nov 2022

- Rebuilt VMWARE datacenters, excelled with Java servers, supported DevOps environment:
- o Teleport, Kubernetes, OpenShift, Nginx, etc.
- Deployed & maintained i-Sight Linux OS & JavaScript application on Azure, AWS, & VMWARE.
- Spearheaded containerized deployment of Yellowfin with Docker, Java, & PostgreSQL.
- Excelled at SQL extract, transform, & load operations for MySQL & PostgreSQL.
- Designed secure backup & storage for global customer base with Azure & cloud storage mounts.
- Improved & maintained Mail/security with mailgateways, encryption keys, Nginx Reverse Proxy, & DNS.
- Audited & provisioned Checkpoint Firewall, Checkpoint VPN, Mail Gateway, & PaloAlto firewall.

Business Analyst (Project)

bioLytical

Richmond, BC

Oct 2021-Nov 2021

- Designed automated Document management: Business process mapping, testing automation prototypes in DDX, & writing TSQL/ SQL code logic doing work on OCR captures.
- Modified SQL Server ddxArchive database to store change management of table attributes (document lookups).
- Configured auto email of Purchase Orders & Sales Orders through supplier & customer lookups & SMTP server integration.
- Mapped documents in Port Form Mapper using OCR, emailed, printed, & archived.
- Enabled secure connections to SQL Server (TSQL & SQL) & Windows Server.
- * Configured doc maps, SQL lookups, & TSQL security in publisher/ viewer apps through DDX Admin.
- Integrated DDX system with SYSPRO with hyperlinks, triggers, auto fill, & programs.
- Secured user interface to DDX with SSO & role based app startup with INI files on Windows.

Other work:

- Resolved Salesforce & SCRIBE (middleware/integration) issues with SYSPRO.
- Reported and created dashboards out of SQL Server backend for SYSPRO with PowerBI & direct SQL queries.
- Effectively tracked change management requests with the iTop ticketing system.

IT Manager (COVID-19 Layoff)

True Mechanical

Burnaby, BC

Sept 2020-Apr 2021

- Reduced costs by screening network, infrastructure, & software asset change requests.
- Optimized compute and software on different classes of workstations.
- Systematically enforced compliance by mapping licensing & working with Microsoft.

Skills

- DevOps (Java, Python, & Node.JS)
- Machine Learning
- Infrastructure as Code (IaC)
- Networking
- ERP (Business Process Mapping)
- Databases
- ❖ ASP.NET
- Access
- SYSPRO
- GCP DevOps